<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Feeney</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Feeney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Tim Feeney</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Significance: why there is nothing significant about it</title>
      <link>/post/clinical-significance-why-there-is-nothing-significant-about-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/clinical-significance-why-there-is-nothing-significant-about-it/</guid>
      <description>I saw a post on twitter recently. You can hear about clinical significance a lot if you go to medical oriented conferences dominated by physicians. It is usually a phrase brought up when presenting results that are not &amp;ldquo;statistically significant.&amp;rdquo; This is a way to justify and lend meaning or import to results that otherwise people would blow off. I argue that this is complete malarkey, and I want to talk about why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stats software compared: A n00bs Viewpoint</title>
      <link>/post/stats-software-compared-a-n00bs-viewpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/stats-software-compared-a-n00bs-viewpoint/</guid>
      <description>While in my MPH training I had the opportunity to use (in class) both Stata and SAS. They were both great, but it became apparent during that time that serious stat were done with R. Further, visualizations that I saw from R packages like ggplot were just so much prettier than anything I saw in SAS or Stata.
There were no specific classes to learn R during my MPH, but I was able to teach myself by taking free online class, googling answer, and just experimenting with my data and comparing it to other software I already knew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction Post</title>
      <link>/post/intro-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/intro-post/</guid>
      <description>What is this blog about and what can I expect? This is my professional site. I am interested broadly in STEM fields and may post on a wide range of topics from paper dissections, discussion of topics, and of course R for statistical analysis.
This tweet
Write a blog post when you learn things, you’ll remember the little thing that’s not in the docs - @dataandme #rladies pic.twitter.com/Hrr51EVwQa
&amp;mdash; R-Ladies Boston 🐟 (@RLadiesBoston) May 30, 2018  got me much more intersted in using this as a learning experience for both myself and anyone who finds their way here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic is a framework to help you create a beautiful website quickly. Perfect for personal sites, blogs, or business/project sites. Check out the latest demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes. Then head on over to the Quick Start guide or take a look at the Release Notes.

Key features:
 Easily manage various content including homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects Extensible via color themes and widgets/plugins Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Social/academic network linking, Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Multilingual and easy to customize  Color Themes Academic is available in different color themes and font themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>